Majdi Abdullah Asiri

SUMMARY

I hold a bachelor's degree in economic and financial sciences and I am currently working as a technical support in the technical management information system in the Ghava pharmacy group, and I have previous experience in customer service and an administrative official in Hijaz Mall very passionate about self-development and a fan of team work.

Majdi.asiri99@gmail.com



0541334551



Makkah, Saudi Arabia



20 April, 1999

EDUCATION

Banking and Financial Markets

Umm al-Qura University

08/2018 - 07/2022

GPA 3.36 of 4 (very Good)

WORK EXPERIENCE

MIS technical support

Ghaya pharmacies

2019 - Present makkah

Information Technology Department-Management Information Systems

Tasks

- Building Promotionsin the system and the website
- Technical Support For Branches
- Customer Service
- Prepare Reports
- Company system supervisor
- Raise and Modify the prices of items and add them

practical training with financial Department Ghaya pharmacies

01/2022 - 06/2022

Makkah

Achievements/Tasks

 University training in a Ghaya company for a period of 5 months in the Department of Finance

Director of Operations

Mutawfi Foundation, pilgrims of Turkey and Muslims of Europe

2015 - 2019 makkah

Tasks

- Contact the Ministry of Hajj
- Receive official documents
- Staff distribution plan in season

Marketing supervisor Hijaz Malls

2017 - 2018 makkah

- Supervising reception staff
- Receive official papers

SKILLS

Professionalism in the use of Office programs

Self-education

Manage stress

CERTIFICATES

IT in the Workplace - Master Microsoft Office

Introduction In Information Technology

Teamwork Skills

Data Analysis

Introduction to Data and Descriptive Analytics

Reviewing and Evaluating Performance in Public Agencies in Light of the Shift to Accrual Based Accounting

Financial Performance Management: Startup Phase

Leadership Essentials

Conversational English Skills for Beginners

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency